<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title></title>
<link>http://liquidunderground.github.io</link>

<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Liquid Underground</copyright>
<managingEditor>Liquid Underground</managingEditor>
<webMaster>Liquid Underground</webMaster>

<generator>Pandoc -- pandoc.org</generator>
<item>
<title>
LiquidLauncher v1.0 released
</title>
<p><link>http://liquidunderground.github.io/blog/20230701-liquidlauncher-v1-released.html</link>
<author>PixL</author> <pubDate>2023-07-01</pubDate></p>
<content>
<p>
At last, <a
href="https://github.com/liquidunderground/liquidlauncher/">LiquidLauncher</a>
finally reached it’s first full version, <code>v1.0</code>. This update
now features both new extension as well as restored old ones, such as
the ability to download mods from within the launcher. Here’s a quick
rundown of the changes
</p>
<h3 id="added-functionality">
Added functionality
</h3>
<ul>
<li>
Support for Skybase and Gamebanana added
</li>
<li>
Support for custom Skins and Colors added
</li>
<li>
SRB2 Flatpak support
</li>
<li>
Added a ridiculous amount of game config options
<ul>
<li>
Dedicated Battlemod support
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
Implemented MS-agnostic room queries
</li>
<li>
Fixed mod downloading
</li>
<li>
Added developer options
</li>
<li>
Added snitch button
</li>
<li>
Implemented multi-row operations for netgame/MS tables
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="quality-of-life">
Quality-of-Life
</h3>
<ul>
<li>
Icons added to game view menu and mod list to distinguish between
modsources
</li>
<li>
Changed Master Server API setting to comboboxes
</li>
<li>
Migrated config formats to TOML
</li>
<li>
Asynchronization of most queries
</li>
<li>
Games are now launched as separate processes
</li>
<li>
Lots of error text and microprint to get started
</li>
</ul>
<p>
Aside from tons of new features and other quality-of-life improvements,
LiquidLauncher now also integrates neatly into our emerging
infrastructure such as our newsfeed and our most popular LiquidMS nodes
such that you can now conveniently access the Underground right from
within LiquidLauncher.
</p>
<p>
Check out our GitHub release at the link below.
</p>
<p>
<a
href="https://github.com/liquidunderground/liquidlauncher/releases/tag/v1.0"
class="uri">https://github.com/liquidunderground/liquidlauncher/releases/tag/v1.0</a>
</p>
<p></content> </item></p>
<item>
<title>
Master Servers and Netgames pages introduction
</title>
<p><link>http://liquidunderground.github.io/blog/20230627-masterservers-and-netgames-introduced.html</link>
<author>PixL</author> <pubDate>2023-06-27</pubDate></p>
<content>
<p>
Liquid Underground’s website now features a dedicated <a
href="https://liquidunderground.github.io/masterservers.html">Master
Servers</a> page! No more sifting through the <code>#featured</code>
channel on Discord and no more need to join our Discord to find out
about what LiquidMS nodes are available to use. As of now, this page is
manually maintained by me and requires either a pull request or a plain
old verbal request towards me for your new nodes to be listed, but I
still hope that this archive will be useful to everyone interested in
utilizing LiquidMS, especially our players.
</p>
<p>
Furthermore, we’ve also launched a <a
href="https://liquidunderground.github.io/netgames.html">Netgames</a>
page to let netgame hosts officially advertise their affiliation with
Liquid Underground and be discovered both by and through our community.
Once again, simply file a pull request or ask for your netgame to be
added to the list, featuring all information necessary for the table on
the site.
</p>
<p>
Thank you for reading<br /> - PixL
</p>
<p></content> </item></p>
<item>
<title>
Liquid Underground Blog launch
</title>
<p><link>http://liquidunderground.github.io/blog/20230621-bloglaunch.html</link>
<author>PixL</author> <pubDate>2023-06-21</pubDate></p>
<content>
<p>
Hello,
</p>
<p>
As this website seemed rather dormant for such a public outlet of Liquid
Underground, I’ve decided to put a blog system into here. In short, it’s
a Makefile-based static site generator based on Pandoc, but for further
details, I suggest looking at the <a
href="https://github.com/liquidunderground/liquidunderground.github.io/">website
repository</a>’s <code>README.md</code>.
</p>
<p>
In order to conveniently relay our news towards <a
href="https://github.com/liquidunderground/liquidlauncher/">LiquidLauncher</a>,
it also features an RSS feed at <a
href="https://liquidunderground.github.io/feed.rss"
class="uri">https://liquidunderground.github.io/feed.rss</a> which will
soon be integrated as the launcher’s default news feed.
</p>
<p>
Naturally, in typical LqU manner, I’ve also added instructions on how to
submit your own articles on here on our <a
href="https://github.com/liquidunderground/liquidunderground.github.io/">website
repository</a>. That way, this blog can serve as a central news outlet
for all the Liquid Underground community wants to share.
</p>
<p>
Thanks<br /> - PixL
</p>
<p></content> </item></p>
</channel>
</rss>
